Association of Canadian Publishers fonds
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department
- Subject files, 1951 - 1984; F-57-5; 4.91 m of textual records ca. 50 photographs; Physical description: 1 photograph located in F-57-5-1-3 Physical description: 26 photographs located in F-57-5-9-11
  - General files, 1975 - 1978; F-57-5-6; 35 cm of textual records
    - Atlantic Publishers Association, 1976 - 1977; F-57-5-6-0-1 (Archival box - standard 57-37)
    - Atlantic Publishers Association, 1977; F-57-5-6-0-2 (Archival box - standard 57-37)
    - Atlantic Publishers Association, 1975 - 1977; F-57-5-6-0-3 (Archival box - standard 57-37)
    - Atlantic Publishers Association, 1977; F-57-5-6-0-4 (Archival box - standard 57-37)
    - A - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1977; F-57-5-6-0-5 (Archival box - standard 57-37)
    - B.P.A.L., 1977 - 1978; F-57-5-6-0-6 (Archival box - standard 57-37)
    - B.P. Report, 1977; F-57-5-6-0-7 (Archival box - standard 57-37)
    - Bibliography on Publishing (ACP), 1976 - 1977; F-57-5-6-0-8 (Archival box - standard 57-37)
    - Book and Periodical Development Council, 1975 - 1977; F-57-5-6-0-9 (Archival box - standard 57-37)
    - Book Publishers Professional Association, 1976 - 1977; F-57-5-6-0-10 (Archival box - standard 57-37)
    - Bowker, R.R., 1976 - 1977; F-57-5-6-0-11 (Archival box - standard 57-37)
    - B.C. Publishers Group - annual meeting, 1976 - 1977; F-57-5-6-0-12 (Archival box - standard 57-37)
    - B.C. Publishers Group - application to B.C. Cultural fund, 1976 - 1977; F-57-5-6-0-13 (Archival box - standard 57-38)
    - B.C. Publishers Group - budgets, 1976 - 1977; F-57-5-6-0-14 (Archival box - standard 57-38)
    - B.C. Publishers Group - catalogues, 1976 - 1977; F-57-5-6-0-15 (Archival box - standard 57-38)
    - B.C. Publishers Group - correspondence, 1976 - 1977; F-57-5-6-0-16 (Archival box - standard 57-38)
    - B - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1976 - 1977; F-57-5-6-0-17 (Archival box - standard 57-38)
    - Canada Counci - Aid to Writing..., 1976 - 1977; F-57-5-6-0-18 (Archival box - standard 57-38)
    - Canada Counci - Block Grant Program, 1977 - 1978; F-57-5-6-0-19 (Archival box - standard 57-38)
    - Canada Counci - Correspondence, 1977 - 1978; F-57-5-6-0-20 (Archival box - standard 57-38)
    - Canada Counci - Press Releases, 1977; F-57-5-6-0-21 (Archival box - standard 57-38)
    - Canadian Basic Books, 1976 - 1977; F-57-5-6-0-22 (Archival box - standard 57-38)
    - Canadian Booksellers Association, 1977; F-57-5-6-0-23 (Archival box - standard 57-38)
    - Canadian Booksellers Association - Bulletin, 1975 - 1977; F-57-5-6-0-24 (Archival box - standard 57-38)
    - Canadian Booksellers Association - Convention, 1976 - 1977; F-57-5-6-0-25 (Archival box - standard 57-38)
    - Canadian Booksellers Association - Trade Mission to Britain, 1976 - 1977; F-57-5-6-0-26 (Archival box - standard 57-38)
    - C, D - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1976 - 1977; F-57-5-6-0-27 (Archival box - standard 57-38)
    - Executive Council and Committees List, 1977; F-57-5-6-0-28 (Archival box - standard 57-39)
    - Financial - budgets, financial statements, 1976 - 1977; F-57-5-6-0-29 (Archival box - standard 57-39)
    - Manitoba Block Grant Brief, 1977; F-57-5-6-0-30 (Archival box - standard 57-39)
    - Membership and Mailing Lists, 1977; F-57-5-6-0-31 (Archival box - standard 57-39)
    - Membership - corresponsence, 1977; F-57-5-6-0-32 (Archival box - standard 57-39)
    - Montreal International Book Fair, 1976 - 1977; F-57-5-6-0-33 (Archival box - standard 57-39)
    - Montreal International Book Fair participation, 1977; F-57-5-6-0-34 (Archival box - standard 57-39)
    - Montreal Book Fair - follow-up, 1977; F-57-5-6-0-35 (Archival box - standard 57-39)
    - Moscow Book Fair, 1976 - 1977; F-57-5-6-0-36 (Archival box - standard 57-39)
    - Office and Employees, 1977; F-57-5-6-0-37 (Archival box - standard 57-39)
    - Pamphlets, 1977; F-57-5-6-0-38 (Archival box - standard 57-39)
    - Symon's Reports; clippings and correspondence, 1976 - 1977; F-57-5-6-0-39 (Archival box - standard 57-39)
  - General files, 1967 - 1979; F-57-5-7; 59 cm of textual records
    - Airport Bookstores, 1976 - 1978; F-57-5-7-0-1 (Archival box - standard 57-39)
    - Alberta Consumer and Corporate Affairs, 1977; F-57-5-7-0-2 (Archival box - standard 57-39)
    - Anti-Inflation Board, 1978; F-57-5-7-0-3 (Archival box - standard 57-40)
    - Association for Canadain Studies in the US, 1977 - 1978; F-57-5-7-0-4 (Archival box - standard 57-40)
    - Association of Canadian Community Colleges, 1977; F-57-5-7-0-5 (Archival box - standard 57-40)
    - Atlantic Provinces - Booksellers Fair, 1978; F-57-5-7-0-6 (Archival box - standard 57-40)
    - Atlantic Publishers Association - correspondence, briefs, 1977 - 1978; F-57-5-7-0-7 (Archival box - standard 57-40)
    - Belford Books, 1978; F-57-5-7-0-8 (Archival box - standard 57-40)
    - Book Awards, 1976 - 1977; F-57-5-7-0-9 (Archival box - standard 57-40)
    - Book Development Council, U.K., 1976 - 1977; F-57-5-7-0-10 (Archival box - standard 57-40)
    - Books Canada Inc., U.S.A., 1976 - 1977; F-57-5-7-0-11 (Archival box - standard 57-40)
    - Books Canada Ltd., 1977 - 1978; F-57-5-7-0-12 (Archival box - standard 57-40)
    - Books for Everybody, 1978; F-57-5-7-0-13 (Archival box - standard 57-40)
    - B.C. Book Purchase Program, 1977; F-57-5-7-0-14 (Archival box - standard 57-40)
    - B.C. Ministry of Education, 1977; F-57-5-7-0-15 (Archival box - standard 57-40)
    - B.C. Library Association, 1977; F-57-5-7-0-16 (Archival box - standard 57-40)
    - B.C. Publishers Group Annual Meeting, 1978; F-57-5-7-0-17 (Archival box - standard 57-40)
    - B.C. Publishers Group, 1978; F-57-5-7-0-18 (Archival box - standard 57-40)
    - British Publishers Trade Mission to Canada, 1967 - 1978; F-57-5-7-0-19 (Archival box - standard 57-40)
    - Canada Council - attacks on, 1978; F-57-5-7-0-20 (Archival box - standard 57-40)
    - Canada Council - Book Purchase Program, 1978; F-57-5-7-0-21 (Archival box - standard 57-40)
    - Canada Council - correspondence, 1978; F-57-5-7-0-22 (Archival box - standard 57-40)
    - Canada Council - Grants, 1978; F-57-5-7-0-23 (Archival box - standard 57-40)
    - Canada Council - 20 + 5, 1978; F-57-5-7-0-24 (Archival box - standard 57-40)
    - Canadian Studies Foundation, 1977 - 1978; F-57-5-7-0-25 (Archival box - standard 57-41)
    - Canadian Association for Information Science, 1977 - 1978; F-57-5-7-0-26 (Archival box - standard 57-41)
    - Canadian Author and Bookman, 1977; F-57-5-7-0-27 (Archival box - standard 57-41)
    - Canadian Book Information Centre 1/2, 1977 - 1979; F-57-5-7-0-28 (Archival box - standard 57-41)
    - Canadian Book Information Centre 2/2, 1977 - 1979; F-57-5-7-0-29 (Archival box - standard 57-41)
    - Canadian Book Information Centre - review committee, 1978; F-57-5-7-0-30 (Archival box - standard 57-41)
    - Canadian Book Publishers Council, 1976 - 1978; F-57-5-7-0-31 (Archival box - standard 57-41)
    - Canadian Booksellers Association, 1978; F-57-5-7-0-32 (Archival box - standard 57-41)
    - Canadian Broadcasting Corporation, 1978; F-57-5-7-0-33 (Archival box - standard 57-41)
    - Canadian Copyright Institute, 1975 - 1978; F-57-5-7-0-34 (Archival box - standard 57-41)
    - Canadian Crafts Council, 1976 - 1977; F-57-5-7-0-35 (Archival box - standard 57-41)
    - Canadian Culture Research Association, 1977; F-57-5-7-0-36 (Archival box - standard 57-41)
    - Canadian Library Association, 1977 - 1978; F-57-5-7-0-37 (Archival box - standard 57-41)
    - Canadian National Institute for the Blind, 1976; F-57-5-7-0-38 (Archival box - standard 57-41)
    - Canadian Publishing Foundation, 1976 - 1977; F-57-5-7-0-39 (Archival box - standard 57-42)
    - Cataloguing in Publicaton, 1976; F-57-5-7-0-40 (Archival box - standard 57-42)
    - Central Ontario Regional Library, 1976 - 1977; F-57-5-7-0-41 (Archival box - standard 57-42)
    - Centre for Northern Studies, 1976 - 1977; F-57-5-7-0-42 (Archival box - standard 57-42)
    - Classic's Policy, 1977; F-57-5-7-0-43 (Archival box - standard 57-42)
    - Combined Book Exhibit, 1977; F-57-5-7-0-44 (Archival box - standard 57-42)
    - Commonwealth Institute Poetry Prize, 1976 - 1977; F-57-5-7-0-45 (Archival box - standard 57-42)
    - Compensation for Authors, 1978; F-57-5-7-0-46 (Archival box - standard 57-42)
    - Conference on the Canadian Novel, 1978; F-57-5-7-0-47 (Archival box - standard 57-42)
    - Conseil Superior du Livre, 1976 - 1978; F-57-5-7-0-48 (Archival box - standard 57-42)
    - Copyright in Canada - brief and correspondence, 1978; F-57-5-7-0-49 (Archival box - standard 57-42)
    - Customs Tariff Board, 1978; F-57-5-7-0-50 (Archival box - standard 57-42)
    - Fitzhenry and Whiteside, 1973 - 1977; F-57-5-7-0-51 (Archival box - standard 57-42)
    - German Embassy, 1978 - 1979; F-57-5-7-0-52 (Archival box - standard 57-42)
    - Greenlan - Paul Bay, book display, 1978 - 1979; F-57-5-7-0-53 (Archival box - standard 57-42)
    - Half-back - Wintario, 1977 - 1978; F-57-5-7-0-54 (Archival box - standard 57-42)
    - Half-back - Wintario, 1977 - 1978; F-57-5-7-0-55 (Archival box - standard 57-42)
    - Half-back - Wintario press clippings, 1977 - 1978; F-57-5-7-0-56 (Archival box - standard 57-42)
    - Half-back - Wintario questionnaire, 1978; F-57-5-7-0-57 (Archival box - standard 57-42)
    - I.S.B.N., 1976 - 1978; F-57-5-7-0-58 (Archival box - standard 57-42)
    - Kakabeka Publishing Company, 1976 - 1977; F-57-5-7-0-59 (Archival box - standard 57-43)
    - McDonald Publishing House Incorporated, 1975 - 1979; F-57-5-7-0-60 (Archival box - standard 57-43)
    - Montreal International Book Fair, 1977 - 1978; F-57-5-7-0-61 (Archival box - standard 57-43)
    - Monzer, Jim, 1977 - 1978; F-57-5-7-0-62 (Archival box - standard 57-43)
    - Music Publishers Group, 1978; F-57-5-7-0-63 (Archival box - standard 57-43)
    - National Book Week, 1975 - 1978; F-57-5-7-0-64 (Archival box - standard 57-43)
    - Ontario Arts Council, 1976 - 1978; F-57-5-7-0-65 (Archival box - standard 57-43)
    - Ontario Arts Council grants, 1975 - 1977; F-57-5-7-0-66 (Archival box - standard 57-43)
    - Ontario Arts Council grants, 1977 - 1978; F-57-5-7-0-67 (Archival box - standard 57-43)
    - Ontario Ministry of Culture and Recreation, 1977 - 1978; F-57-5-7-0-68 (Archival box - standard 57-43)
    - Ontario Ministry of Education, 1975 - 1978; F-57-5-7-0-69 (Archival box - standard 57-43)
    - Ontario Provincial Library Council, 1977; F-57-5-7-0-70 (Archival box - standard 57-43)
    - Ontario Provincial Library Service - Brief to the Royal Commission on Violence in the Communications Indsutry, 1976; F-57-5-7-0-71 (Archival box - standard 57-43)
    - Postal Strike, 1976; F-57-5-7-0-72 (Archival box - standard 57-43)
    - Postal Strike, 1975 - 1978; F-57-5-7-0-73 (Archival box - standard 57-43)
    - President's Reports - Western Tour, 1978; F-57-5-7-0-74 (Archival box - standard 57-43)
    - Press Releases, 1977 - 1978; F-57-5-7-0-75 (Archival box - standard 57-43)
    - Statistics Canada Survey - Reading Habits in Canada, 1977 - 1978; F-57-5-7-0-76 (Archival box - standard 57-44)
    - Secretary of State - Publishing Policy, 1975 - 1979; F-57-5-7-0-77 (Archival box - standard 57-44)
    - Secretary of State, 1977; F-57-5-7-0-78 (Archival box - standard 57-44)
    - Secretary of State - Study of Cultural Services Organizations, 1977; F-57-5-7-0-79 (Archival box - standard 57-44)
    - Wintario Funds to Public Libraries, 1976 - 1978; F-57-5-7-0-80 (Archival box - standard 57-44)
    - Writers Union of Canada, 1976 - 1978; F-57-5-7-0-81 (Archival box - standard 57-44)
    - W - Miscellaneous, 1977 - 1978; F-57-5-7-0-82 (Archival box - standard 57-44)
  - General files, 1974 - 1980; F-57-5-8; 41 cm of textual records
    - Alberta Publishers Assocation, 1977 - 1979; F-57-5-8-0-1 (Archival box - standard 57-44)
    - Association of Book Publishers of B.C., 1978 - 1979; F-57-5-8-0-2 (Archival box - standard 57-44)
    - Association of Book Publishers of B.C., 1979; F-57-5-8-0-3 (Archival box - standard 57-44)
    - Association of Book Publishers of B.C., 1978 - 1979; F-57-5-8-0-4 (Archival box - standard 57-44)
    - Association of Canadian Publishers History, 1979; F-57-5-8-0-5 (Archival box - standard 57-45)
    - Atlantic Publishers Association - budget, 1978; F-57-5-8-0-6 (Archival box - standard 57-45)
    - Atlantic Publishers Association - correspondence, 1979; F-57-5-8-0-7 (Archival box - standard 57-45)
    - Australia Publishers Association, 1975 - 1976; F-57-5-8-0-8 (Archival box - standard 57-45)
    - Book and Periodical Development Council, 1977 - 1979; F-57-5-8-0-9 (Archival box - standard 57-45)
    - B.P.D.C. 1812 Committee - correspondence, 1978; F-57-5-8-0-10 (Archival box - standard 57-45)
    - B.P.D.C., Freedom of Information Press Conference, 1979; F-57-5-8-0-11 (Archival box - standard 57-45)
    - British Columbia Publishers Group, 1978; F-57-5-8-0-12 (Archival box - standard 57-45)
    - British Columbia Publishing Assistance, 1978; F-57-5-8-0-13 (Archival box - standard 57-45)
    - Canada Council, correspondence, 1978 - 1980; F-57-5-8-0-14 (Archival box - standard 57-45)
    - Canada Council, budget request, 1978 - 1979; F-57-5-8-0-15 (Archival box - standard 57-45)
    - Canada Council, block grant funding, 1978; F-57-5-8-0-16 (Archival box - standard 57-45)
    - Canadian Book Information Centre, 1979; F-57-5-8-0-17 (Archival box - standard 57-45)
    - Canadian Book Publishers Council, 1979; F-57-5-8-0-18 (Archival box - standard 57-45)
    - Canadian Booksellers Association - Toronto Convention '79, 1978 - 1979; F-57-5-8-0-19 (Archival box - standard 57-45)
    - Canadian Conference on the Arts, 1979; F-57-5-8-0-20 (Archival box - standard 57-45)
    - Canadian Publishers Project Co-ordinating Committee, 1979; F-57-5-8-0-21 (Archival box - standard 57-46)
    - Canlit, 1978 - 1979; F-57-5-8-0-22 (Archival box - standard 57-46)
    - Industry Trade and Commerce, Deptartment of, 1978 - 1980; F-57-5-8-0-23 (Archival box - standard 57-46)
    - International Piracy Survey, 1979; F-57-5-8-0-24 (Archival box - standard 57-46)
    - International Publishers Association, 1975 - 1979; F-57-5-8-0-25 (Archival box - standard 57-46)
    - McGill Queen's University Press, 1977; F-57-5-8-0-26 (Archival box - standard 57-46)
    - Membership - memoranda to, 1978; F-57-5-8-0-27 (Archival box - standard 57-46)
    - Membership - memoranda to, 1979; F-57-5-8-0-28 (Archival box - standard 57-46)
    - Ontario Arts Council budget applications, 1978; F-57-5-8-0-29 (Archival box - standard 57-46)
    - Ontario Arts Council correspondence, 1978; F-57-5-8-0-30 (Archival box - standard 57-46)
    - Ontario Ministry of Culture and Recreation, 1978 - 1979; F-57-5-8-0-31 (Archival box - standard 57-46)
    - Ontario Taxation, 1979; F-57-5-8-0-32 (Archival box - standard 57-46)
    - Organization (of IPA/ACP), 1974 - 1977; F-57-5-8-0-33 (Archival box - standard 57-46)
    - Oromocto Canadian Literature Prize, 1977 - 1979; F-57-5-8-0-34 (Archival box - standard 57-47)
    - The Publishers Association, U.K., 1975 - 1979; F-57-5-8-0-35 (Archival box - standard 57-47)
    - Publishing Centre - Supply and Services Canada (formerly Info Canada), 1975 - 1979; F-57-5-8-0-36 (Archival box - standard 57-47)
    - Rights Canadian, 1978 - 1979; F-57-5-8-0-37 (Archival box - standard 57-47)
    - Secretary of State, 1978; F-57-5-8-0-38 (Archival box - standard 57-47)
    - Secretary of State, 1979 - 1980; F-57-5-8-0-39 (Archival box - standard 57-47)
    - Secretary of State - Publishing Policy Advisory Committee, 1979; F-57-5-8-0-40 (Archival box - standard 57-47)
    - Secretary of State - Speech to Annual General Meeting, 1979; F-57-5-8-0-41 (Archival box - standard 57-47)
    - State of the Industry Survey, 1978 - 1979; F-57-5-8-0-42 (Archival box - standard 57-47)
    - Subway Campaign, 1979; F-57-5-8-0-43 (Archival box - standard 57-47)
    - Writer's Union of Canada, 1979; F-57-5-8-0-44 (Archival box - standard 57-47)
  - General files, 1974 - 1983; F-57-5-9; 1.27 m of textual records
    - Academy of Canadian Writers, 1978 - 1980; F-57-5-9-0-1 (Archival box - standard 57-47)
    - Adams, Ian: defense for, 1980 - 1981; F-57-5-9-0-2 (Archival box - standard 57-47)
    - Advertising and Publicity, 1980 - 1981; F-57-5-9-0-3 (Archival box - standard 57-48)
    - Alberta Department of Education, 1979 - 1981; F-57-5-9-0-4 (Archival box - standard 57-48)
    - Alberta Heritage Trust, 1978 - 1979; F-57-5-9-0-5 (Archival box - standard 57-48)
    - Alberta Ministry of Culture, 1979 - 1980; F-57-5-9-0-6 (Archival box - standard 57-48)
    - Alberta Publishers Association, 1980; F-57-5-9-0-7 (Archival box - standard 57-48)
    - Aldana, Patsy: memoranda to, 1979 - 1980; F-57-5-9-0-8 (Archival box - standard 57-48)
    - American Booksellers Association, 1981; F-57-5-9-0-9 (Archival box - standard 57-48)
    - Ampersand - The Book Trade in Canada, 1978 - 1981; F-57-5-9-0-10 (Archival box - standard 57-48)
    - Annual General Meetings - press release, photo, 1979 - 1981; F-57-5-9-0-11 (Archival box - standard 57-48)
    - Applebaum - Hebert, briefs and submissions, 1981; F-57-5-9-0-12 (Archival box - standard 57-48)
    - Applebaum - Hebert, briefs and submissions, 1981; F-57-5-9-0-13 (Archival box - standard 57-48)
    - Association des Editeurs Canadiens, 1978 - 1982; F-57-5-9-0-14 (Archival box - standard 57-48)
    - Association of American Publishers, 1976 - 1980; F-57-5-9-0-15 (Archival box - standard 57-48)
    - Association of Book Publishers of B.C. - Agendas, Minutes and Papers, 1979 - 1980; F-57-5-9-0-16 (Archival box - standard 57-48)
    - Association of Book Publishers of B.C., 1980 - 1981; F-57-5-9-0-17 (Archival box - standard 57-48)
    - Association of Book Publishers of B.C. - Survey of Book Publishing, 1981; F-57-5-9-0-18 (Archival box - standard 57-48)
    - Association of Book Publishers of B.C., 1982 - 1983; F-57-5-9-0-19 (Archival box - standard 57-48)
    - Association of Manitoba Book Publishers, 1980; F-57-5-9-0-20 (Archival box - standard 57-49)
    - Atlantic Publishers Association, 1980; F-57-5-9-0-21 (Archival box - standard 57-49)
    - Australia Book Publishers Association, 1978 - 1980; F-57-5-9-0-22 (Archival box - standard 57-49)
    - Australia Market Report - J.J. Douglas, 1978; F-57-5-9-0-23 (Archival box - standard 57-49)
    - A - Miscellaneous Corresponsence, 1979 - 1983; F-57-5-9-0-24 (Archival box - standard 57-49)
    - Backlist Special Report - Publishers Weekly, 1979; F-57-5-9-0-25 (Archival box - standard 57-49)
    - Balmuir Publishing, 1981; F-57-5-9-0-26 (Archival box - standard 57-49)
    - Banff Publishing Workshop, 1981; F-57-5-9-0-27 (Archival box - standard 57-49)
    - Beaufort Books, 1980; F-57-5-9-0-28 (Archival box - standard 57-49)
    - Big Books Study Proposal - Children's Committees, 1980; F-57-5-9-0-29 (Archival box - standard 57-49)
    - Birmingham, U.K. Canada Days, 1980 - 1981; F-57-5-9-0-30 (Archival box - standard 57-49)
    - Block Grant brief, 1979; F-57-5-9-0-31 (Archival box - standard 57-49)
    - Book, definition of, 1977 - 1980; F-57-5-9-0-32 (Archival box - standard 57-49)
    - Book Post Survey, 1980; F-57-5-9-0-33 (Archival box - standard 57-49)
    - Book Publishers Professional Association, 1979 - 1981; F-57-5-9-0-34 (Archival box - standard 57-49)
    - Books for Everybody (catalogue), 1979 - 1983; F-57-5-9-0-35 (Archival box - standard 57-49)
    - The Bookseller, 1981; F-57-5-9-0-36 (Archival box - standard 57-49)
    - Brazil Publishing, 1980; F-57-5-9-0-37 (Archival box - standard 57-49)
    - British Columbia Ministry of Education, 1977 - 1979; F-57-5-9-0-38 (Archival box - standard 57-50)
    - British Publishers Association, 1977 - 1979; F-57-5-9-0-39 (Archival box - standard 57-50)
    - Broadcasting Standing Committee - Minutes, 1979; F-57-5-9-0-40 (Archival box - standard 57-50)
    - B - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1979 - 1983; F-57-5-9-0-41 (Archival box - standard 57-50)
    - Calgary Public Library, 1978 - 1981; F-57-5-9-0-42 (Archival box - standard 57-50)
    - Calgary School Board, 1978; F-57-5-9-0-43 (Archival box - standard 57-50)
    - Canada Council - aid to artists, 1976 - 1980; F-57-5-9-0-45 (Archival box - standard 57-50)
    - Canada Council - block grants, 1979 - 1982; F-57-5-9-0-46 (Archival box - standard 57-50)
    - Canada Council - budget requests, 1979 - 1981; F-57-5-9-0-47 (Archival box - standard 57-50)
    - Canada Council - correspondence, 1981; F-57-5-9-0-48 (Archival box - standard 57-50)
    - Canadian Association of Motion Picture Producers, 1979; F-57-5-9-0-49 (Archival box - standard 57-50)
    - Canadian Authors Assocation, 1976 - 1981; F-57-5-9-0-50 (Archival box - standard 57-50)
    - Canadian Book Information Centre Media List, 1979; F-57-5-9-0-51 (Archival box - standard 57-50)
    - Canadian Book Manufacturer's Association, 1981; F-57-5-9-0-52 (Archival box - standard 57-50)
    - Canadian Booksellers Association, 1980 - 1981; F-57-5-9-0-53 (Archival box - standard 57-50)
    - Canadian Booksellers Association, 1979 - 1982; F-57-5-9-0-54 (Archival box - standard 57-50)
    - Canadian Books in Print, 1981; F-57-5-9-0-55 (Archival box - standard 57-50)
    - Canadian Conference on the Arts, 1980; F-57-5-9-0-56 (Archival box - standard 57-50)
    - Canadian Conference on the Arts, 1981; F-57-5-9-0-57 (Archival box - standard 57-51)
    - Canadian Periodical Publishers, 1976 - 1980; F-57-5-9-0-58 (Archival box - standard 57-51)
    - Canadian Public Policy Journal, 1979 - 1980; F-57-5-9-0-59 (Archival box - standard 57-51)
    - Canadian Publishing: An Industrial Strategy, 1980 - 1981; F-57-5-9-0-60 (Archival box - standard 57-51)
    - Canadian Report, 1979 - 1982; F-57-5-9-0-61 (Archival box - standard 57-51)
    - Canadian School Trustees Association, 1980; F-57-5-9-0-62 (Archival box - standard 57-51)
    - Canadian Standards Association, 1981; F-57-5-9-0-63 (Archival box - standard 57-51)
    - Canadian Studies, 1979; F-57-5-9-0-64 (Archival box - standard 57-51)
    - Canadian Studies Catalogue, 1980; F-57-5-9-0-65 (Archival box - standard 57-51)
    - Canadian Studies - England, 1980 - 1981; F-57-5-9-0-66 (Archival box - standard 57-51)
    - Canadian Studies - Italy, 1979 - 1981; F-57-5-9-0-67 (Archival box - standard 57-51)
    - Canadian Studies - Japan, 1980; F-57-5-9-0-68 (Archival box - standard 57-51)
    - Canadian Studies - Overseas, 1980; F-57-5-9-0-69 (Archival box - standard 57-51)
    - Canadian Teachers Federation, 1978; F-57-5-9-0-70 (Archival box - standard 57-51)
    - Canadian Teachers Federation, 1981; F-57-5-9-0-71 (Archival box - standard 57-51)
    - Canlit, 1980; F-57-5-9-0-72 (Archival box - standard 57-51)
    - Children's Book Centre, 1977 - 1979; F-57-5-9-0-73 (Archival box - standard 57-51)
    - Children's Book Reviewers and Publishers, 1979 - 1980; F-57-5-9-0-74 (Archival box - standard 57-51)
    - China Media Industry, 1980; F-57-5-9-0-75 (Archival box - standard 57-51)
    - Classics Book Shops, 1980; F-57-5-9-0-76 (Archival box - standard 57-51)
    - CLOUT - Ontario Cultural Alliance, 1980; F-57-5-9-0-77 (Archival box - standard 57-51)
    - Commission of Inquiry on Educational Leave and Productivity, 1978; F-57-5-9-0-78 (Archival box - standard 57-51)
    - Committee for an Independent Canada, 1977 - 1981; F-57-5-9-0-79 (Archival box - standard 57-51)
    - COSMEP - Newsletter, 1980; F-57-5-9-0-80 (Archival box - standard 57-51)
    - Culture Ministers Conference, 1980; F-57-5-9-0-81 (Archival box - standard 57-51)
    - Direct Mail, 1980 - 1982; F-57-5-9-0-82 (Archival box - standard 57-51)
    - Discounts, 1979; F-57-5-9-0-83 (Archival box - standard 57-51)